visadd.com 2014-05-17

# VisAdd - Privacy Policy

* * *

This Privacy Policy (the "Policy") explains how VisAdd may collect and use certain personal information obtained through this Website.

**Personal Information**

VisAdd may request your name and e-mail ("Personal Information") in order to correspond with you, update you with information that we consider may be of interest to you and notify you about various events. VisAdd may share non-personal, anonymous, summary or aggregate user data with certain affiliates and other third parties. You will always have the option of "unsubscribing" from our mailing list at any time, thereby disabling any further such e-mail communication from being sent to you. If you wish to have specific communications with a member of VisAdd, you may send a direct massage via email or fax to the addresses and numbers provided in our Website. VisAdd will not disclose, sell, or rent any of your identifiable personal information to any third party, unless approved by you, or required by law.

**Cookies**

Cookies are small pieces of data that are transferred to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser from our Web Server. A cookie cannot read data from your hard disk or read cookie files that may have been created from other sites. Our Website utilizes cookies as a means of providing personalization features to our visitors. For example, we utilize cookies to remember settings that you may have made at our Website. You can choose whether to accept cookies by changing the settings of your browser. Typically, by accessing the browser's help feature you can obtain information on how to prevent your browser from accepting all cookies or to notify you when a cookie is being sent. If you choose not to accept these cookies, your experience at our Website and other websites may be diminished and some features may not work as intended.

**Links to Other Websites**

When you enter other websites using links from this Website you are entering a website for which VisAdd has no responsibility. VisAdd is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. We highly recommend you review the privacy policies of the websites you are linked to using this Website.

**Security**

VisAdd employs security measures to prevent unauthorized access to the information we collect through this Website. However, VisAdd cannot guarantee that your personal information will never be disclosed in a manner inconsistent with this Policy.

**Changes of Privacy Policy and/or Terms**

VisAdd reserves the right to change this Policy and/or these Terms from time to time. Please check this page frequently and particularly before you submit additional personal information using this Website.

**Governing Law and Forum**

These Terms shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the State of Israel, without giving effect to any principles of conflicts of law. Any dispute between you and VisAdd regarding the content or use of the Website shall be resolved at the exclusive jurisdiction of the competent courts of located in the city of Tel Aviv-Jaffa, Israel.

**Non-Waiver and Severability**

VisAdd's failure to insist upon strict enforcement of any provision of these Terms shall not be construed as a waiver of any provision or right. If any provision of these Terms is found to be void or unenforceable, such provision shall be severed and all other provisions shall remain in force.

**Contact Us**

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this Policy, please feel free to contact us at to [info@VisAdd.com](mailto:info@VisAdd.com)
